<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Broadening Participation in Data Mining - BPDM 2013</title>
		<link>http://www.dataminingshop.com/</link>
		<description>Latest News From BPDM</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<copyright>Copyright 2013 Broadening Participation in Data Mining - BPDM 2013</copyright>
		<lastBuildDate>wed, 23 Jan 2013</lastBuildDate>
		
		
		
		
		
		
		
	<item><title>BPDM 2012 is archived! </title><description>The Broadening Participation in Data Mining 2012 was a huge success with 22 participants selected from 70 applicants. Hope you will join us for BPDM 2013!</description><guid>0</guid><link>/2012/</link><author>brandeis@purdue.edu</author><pubDate>2-15-2013</pubDate></item><item><title>Call for Social Media Coordinator</title><description>Are you interested in being our Social Media Coordinator and attending BPDM 2013?  Click &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=socialMedia.php&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt; for more information.</description><guid>1</guid><link>/2013/socialMedia.php</link><author>soarescv@gmail.com</author><pubDate>2-15-2013</pubDate></item><item><title>Women in Analytics, Data Science, Data Mining?</title><description>While most people in this field are men, there is a growing number of women in this field, loosely defined as union of Analytics, Business Intelligence, Data Science, Data Mining, Machine Learning, and Text Analytics. Here are some of the currently active ones...&lt;a href=\"http://www.kdnuggets.com/2012/06/women-data-scientists-data-miners.html\"&gt;Link&lt;/a&gt; </description><guid>2</guid><link>/2013/news.php</link><author>soarescv@gmail.com</author><pubDate>2-19-2013</pubDate></item><item><title>U.S. NSF - Why Diversity in CS is important</title><description>Computer science professionals of a variety of backgrounds and views discuss why it is imperative for the field to embrace a diversity of perspectives to address today\'s global challenges. &lt;a href=\"http://www.nsf.gov/news/mmg/mmg_disp.cfm?med_id=73862\"&gt;Click here for more.&lt;/a&gt;</description><guid>3</guid><link>/2013/news.php</link><author/><pubDate>3-22-2013</pubDate></item><item><title>Interested in attending BPDM?</title><description>Attendance to BPDM is open to everyone, however for logistic purposes, we require you to send an email request by July 30th to us requesting attendance.  Please include name, title, institution/organization. </description><guid>4</guid><link>/2013/news.php</link><author>brandeis@purdue.edu</author><pubDate>6-11-2013</pubDate></item><item><title>Live Streaming Data Science Keynotes, Aug 9-10</title><description>Virtually join the BPDM program (co-located with ACM SIGKDD 2013 in Chicago), to watch keynotes streamed live Aug 9 and 10, 8:30 am CT.  Click on RSS Title to learn more or find the links under our Agenda tab.</description><guid>5</guid><link>/2013/liveStream.php</link><author>soarescv@gmail.com</author><pubDate>8-8-2013</pubDate></item></channel>
</rss>
